Guide to the Albert C. Woodroof and A. C. Woodroof, Jr. Papers and Architectural Drawings
Albert C. Woodroof and A. C. Woodroof, Jr. Papers and Architectural Drawings
1927-1986
1927 1986
Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986
Woodroof A. C. (Albert Cecil) Jr. 1920-1991
MC 00325
The Albert C. Woodroof and A. C. Woodroof, Jr. Papers and Architectural Drawings document the professional activities of the two architects and their firms. The collection is arranged into five series: drawings, project files, office records, professional papers, and personal papers. The drawings series contains drawings from both Woodroof, Sr. and Woodroof, Jr., and includes floor plans, site plans, details, and elevations for a variety of projects. Project files contain correspondence, financial records, contracts and agreements, and other material relating primarily to Woodroof, Jr.’s firm. Office records contain correspondence, lists of prospective clients, personnel files, financial accounts, and promotional materials for Woodroof, Jr.’s firm. Professional papers contain general materials relating to architecture and design, such as publications from the American Institute of Architects and other professional organizations, catalogs, brochures, and clippings. Personal papers contain correspondence and financial records for both men. Materials in this collection range in date from 1927 to 1986.
Albert Cecil Woodroof (1895-1986) was an architect based in Greensboro, North Carolina. Woodroof received his architectural license in 1927. He worked for several firms throughout the Southeast before opening his own firm in 1935. His projects included residences, churches, and schools. Albert Cecil Woodroof, Jr. (1920-1991) was an architect based in Greensboro, North Carolina. He received a Bachelor of Science in Commerce from the University of North Carolina in 1940. From 1948 to 1963, Woodroof worked in the architectural firm of his father, Albert C. Woodroof, Sr., first as a draftsman and later as a partner. In 1964 Woodroof, Jr. opened his own firm, and later partnered with John S. MacRae and Martin A. Senell. Woodroof’s projects include churches, schools, museums, country clubs, shopping centers, and residences, primarily in North Carolina.
65.5 linear feet
North Carolina State University Libraries, Special Collections Research Center
Donated by Albert Woodroof III (Accession no. 2002.0015).
The collection is arranged into the following series: DrawingsProject FilesOffice RecordsProfessional PapersPersonal Papers
Albert Cecil Woodroof (1895-1986) was an architect based in Greensboro, North Carolina. Woodroof received his architectural license in 1927. He worked for several firms throughout the Southeast before opening his own firm in 1935. His projects included residences, churches, and schools. His son, A. C. Woodroof, Jr., worked for him prior to establishing his own architectural firm. Woodroof was a veteran of World War I. His wife was Mary Woodroof.
Albert Cecil Woodroof, Jr. (1920-1991) was an architect based in Greensboro, North Carolina. He received a Bachelor of Science in Commerce from the University of North Carolina in 1940. From 1948 to 1963, Woodroof worked in the architectural firm of his father, Albert C. Woodroof, Sr., first as a draftsman and later as a partner. In 1964 Woodroof, Jr. opened his own firm, and later partnered with John S. MacRae and Martin A. Senell. Woodroof’s projects include churches, schools, museums, country clubs, shopping centers, and residences, primarily in North Carolina. Woodroof was married to Betty McCall Woodroof and had four children.
The Albert C. Woodroof and A. C. Woodroof, Jr. papers and architectural drawings document the professional activities of the two architects and their firms. The collection is arranged into five series: drawings, project files, office records, professional papers, and personal papers. The drawings series contains drawings from both Woodroof, Sr. and Woodroof, Jr., and includes floor plans, site plans, details, and elevations for a variety of projects. Project files contain correspondence, financial records, contracts and agreements, and other material relating primarily to Woodroof, Jr.’s firm. Office records contain correspondence, lists of prospective clients, personnel files, financial accounts, and promotional materials for Woodroof, Jr.’s firm. Professional papers contain general materials relating to architecture and design, such as publications from the American Institute of Architects and other professional organizations, catalogs, brochures, and clippings. Personal papers contain correspondence and financial records for both men. Materials in this collection range in date from 1927 to 1986.
Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Woodroof A. C. (Albert Cecil) Jr. 1920-1991; Woodroof A. C. (Albert Cecil) Jr. 1920-1991; American Institute of Architects; American Institute of Architects North Carolina Chapter; Woodroof Albert C. III; North Carolina Designs and plans Church buildings; Buildings, structures, etc. Greensboro (N.C.); Designs and plans Public buildings; Design and construction Church buildings; Design and construction School buildings; North Carolina Architectural firms; North Carolina Designs and plans Museum buildings; North Carolina Designs and plans Architecture, Domestic; North Carolina Designs and plans Shopping centers; North Carolina Designs and plans Rehabilitation centers; North Carolina Designs and plans School buildings; Architecture; North Carolina Architects
- Drawings, 1927-1977; 1927 1977
  The drawings series contains drawings from both Woodroof, Sr. and Woodroof, Jr., and includes floor plans, site plans, details, and elevations for a variety of projects.
  - A. C. Woodroof Jr. Drawings, 1927-1976; 1927 1976
    - 601 North Elm Street Building, 1961 (Tube 187)
      Hartmann Charles C.; Greensboro (N.C.)
    - 601 North Elm Street Building: Proposed ramp and new parking deck, 1961 (Flatfolder 2)
      Reproductions
      Greensboro (N.C.)
    - 1600 North Elm Building (Tube 130)
      Woodroof and Associates, Architects, Inc.; Greensboro (N.C.)
    - A. K. Moore Reality Co.: Residence, 1935 (Tube 81)
      Plans, elevations
    - ABC Retail Store (Flatfolder 14)
    - ABC Retail Store, 1968-1969 (Tube 46)
      Details, sections, site plan, schedules
    - ABC Retail Store, 1969 (Tube 60)
      Elevation, floor plans
    - ABC Retail Store, 1969 (Tube 177)
    - ABC Retail Store: Number 12 (Tube 58)
      Elevations, floor plan
      Woodroof A. C. (Albert Cecil) Jr. 1920-1991
    - Allen Junior High School and Mendenhall Junior High School: Walkway canopies, 1969 (Tube 122)
      Electrical plan, diagrams, floor plans, sections
      McMinn Norfleet & Wicker; Greensboro (N.C.)
    - Allen Junior High School and Mendenhall Junior High School: Walkway canopies, 1969 (Flatfolder 15)
    - Armco Country Club: Suspension bridge, 1969 (Tube 68)
      Woodroof and Associates, Architects, Inc.; Middletown (Ohio)
    - Armfield (W. J., III) land-use analysis, 1970 (Tube 49)
      Woodroof and Associates, Architects, Inc.
    - Bank of Reidsville, 1969 (Tube 41)
      Floor plans, sketches
      Woodroof and Associates, Architects, Inc.; Reidsville (N.C.)
    - Bank of Reidsville: Scales Street branch, 1969 (Tube 170)
      Floor plan, elevations, plot plan
      Woodroof and MacRae, Architects, Inc.; Reidsville (N.C.)
    - Beard Buildings, Inc.: Elm Street building, 1970 (Tube 58)
      Floor plans
    - Beard Buildings, Inc.: Office building, 1970 (Tube 129)
      108 State Street, Greensboro, N.C.
    - Beard Buildings, Inc.: Office building, 1970 (Tube 32)
      Foundation, sections, plot plans, main entrance, floor plans, elevations
    - Beard Buildings, Inc.: Office building, 1970 (Tube 39)
    - Beard Buildings, Inc.: Office building, 1970 (Tube 40)
      Floor plans, framing plan, site plan
    - Beard Buildings, Inc.: Office building, 1970 (Tube 59)
      Lighting plan, fixture schedule, power plan
    - Beard Buildings, Inc.: Office building, 1970 (Flatfolder 10)
    - Beard Buildings, Inc.: Proposed office building, 1970 (Tube 177)
    - Beechwood High School: New building addition (Tube 187)
    - Benevolent and Protective Order of Elks, 1966 (Tube 72)
      Woodroof A. C. (Albert Cecil) Jr. 1920-1991; Greensboro (N.C.)
    - Benevolent and Protective Order of Elks: Lodge No. 602, 1965 (Tube 12)
      Floor plans, electrical plans, plumbing plans
    - Benevolent and Protective Order of Elks: Lodge No. 602, 1965 (Tube 63)
      Framing details, elevations, fixture schedule, floor plan, plot plan, foundation plan, kitchen plan, plumbing plan, electrical plan, equipment plan
    - Benevolent and Protective Order of Elks: Lodge No. 602, 1965 (Tube 99)
      HTG, air conditioning plan
    - Benevolent and Protective Order of Elks: Lodge No. 602, 1965 (Tube 168)
      Door schedule and details finish schedule
    - Benevolent and Protective Order of Elks: Lodge No. 602, 1967 (Tube 177)
    - Bessemer Elementary School, 1966 (Tube 55)
      Site plan
    - Bessemer Elementary School, 1967 (Flatfolder 10)
      Woodroof and MacRae, Architects, Inc.; Greensboro (N.C.)
    - Bessemer Elementary School (1 of 2) (Flatfolder 5)
    - Bessemer Elementary School (2 of 2) (Tube 123)
    - Bessemer Junior High School (1 of 2), 1967 (Tube 186)
    - Bessemer Junior High School (2 of 2), 1967 (Tube 190)
    - Bessemer Junior High School, 1967 (Flatfolder 4)
    - Bessemer Junior High School: Demolition and addition (1 of 2), 1967 (Tube 60)
      Floor plan, color schedule
    - Bessemer Junior High School: Demolition and addition (2 of 2), 1967 (Tube 70)
      Roof plan, floor plans, elevations, HVAC
    - Bessemer Junior High School: Demolition of obsolete facilities and addition, 1967 (Tube 132)
    - Bessemer Junior High School: Demolition of obsolete facilities and addition, 1967 (Tube 168)
      Roof plan: South portion and canopy details
    - Bessemer Junior High School: Demolition of obsolete facilities and addition, 1967 (Tube 168)
      Survey and overall site plan
    - Bessemer School (Flatfolder 14)
    - Bisher Hosiery Plant: Alteration and addition, 1964 (Tube 103)
      Woodroof A. C. (Albert Cecil) Jr. 1920-1991; Denton (N.C.)
    - Black Cadillac-Oldsmobile, Inc., 1965 (Tube 171)
      Plot pan, foundation plan, floor plans, elevations, sections, details
    - Black Cadillac-Oldsmobile, Inc., 1965 (Tube 163)
      Plot plan, electrical layouts, schedules, riser diagrams
    - Black Cadillac-Oldsmobile, Inc., 1965 (Tube 33)
      Floor plans, foundation plans, elevations, proposed building
    - Black Cadillac-Oldsmobile, Inc., 1965 (Tube 34)
      Foundation plan, floor plans, elevations, finish schedule, wall sections, alternate steel framing plan
    - Black Cadillac-Oldsmobile, Inc.: New building, 1960 (Flatfolder 2)
    - C. L. Price, Inc.: Office building, 1971 (Tube 59)
      Elevation plans
    - Capps (Mr. S. H.) residence: Porch addition, 1964 (Tube 59)
    - Ciba Geigy Office Building, 1973-1974 (Tube 15)
      Index of drawings, site plans, details, floor plans, doors and hardware, elevations, building sections
      Odell Associates Inc.; Greensboro (N.C.)
    - Ciba Geigy Office Building, 1974 (Tube 16)
      Wall sections, details, stair plans, elevator plans, toilet plan, basement plan, floor plans, lighting plan
    - Coates Hot Water Storage Tank, 1971 (Tube 189)
    - Clyde A. Erwin Elementary School (1 of 2) (Tube 124)
    - Clyde A. Erwin Elementary School (2 of 2) (Flatfolder 9)
    - Clyde A. Erwin Elementary School, 1968 (Tube 114)
    - Clyde A. Erwin Elementary School: Addition, 1967 (Tube 94)
      Sections, plans, roof framing
    - Clyde A. Erwin Elementary School: Addition, 1967-1971 (Tube 69)
      Site plan, sections, floor plans, elevations, doors and windows
    - Clyde A. Erwin Elementary School: Addition, 1971 (Tube 170)
    - Clyde A. Erwin Elementary School: Addition, 1972 (Tube 71)
      Sections, details
    - Clyde A. Erwin Elementary School: Waterline addition, 1968 (Tube 80)
    - College Place Methodist Church: Design for pulpit, 1957 (Tube 84)
    - Denny (Mr. and Mrs. Edwin H.) residence, 1964 (Tube 55)
      Front steps and terrace
    - Dockery Lumber Company: Office and shop building (Tube 170)
      Unfinished schedule
    - Dockery Lumber Company: Proposed alterations, 1969 (Tube 42)
      Elevations, sections, cornices
    - Dockery Lumber Company: Proposed alterations, 1969 (Tube 59)
      Sections
    - Downtown development area, 1971 (Tube 179)
    - Dunhill Food Equipment Corporation, 1968 (Tube 186)
      Woodroof, MacRae and Senell Architects; Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)
    - E. N. Beard Hardwoods, Inc., 1970 (Tube 130)
    - Fellowship Hall, Inc.: Rehabilitation Center (Tube 169)
      Floor plan, cornice details
    - Fellowship Hall, Inc.: Rehabilitation Center (1 of 4), 1970 (Tube 187)
    - Fellowship Hall, Inc.: Rehabilitation Center (2 of 4), 1970; Woodroof and Associates, Architects, Inc. (Tube 234)
    - Fellowship Hall, Inc.: Rehabilitation Center (3 of 4), 1970; Woodroof and Associates, Architects, Inc. (Tube 235)
    - Fellowship Hall, Inc.: Rehabilitation Center (4 of 4), 1970 (Flatfolder 10)
    - Fellowship Hall, Inc.: Rehabilitation Center (1 of 4), 1970 (Tube 106)
    - Fellowship Hall, Inc.: Rehabilitation Center (2 of 4), 1970 (Flatfolder 16)
    - Fellowship Hall, Inc.: Rehabilitation Center (3 of 4), 1970 (Flatfolder 14)
    - Fellowship Hall, Inc.: Rehabilitation Center (4 of 4) (Tube 60)
    - Fellowship Hall, Inc.: Rehabilitation Center, 1970 (Tube 72)
      Elevation, floor plan
    - Fellowship Hall, Inc.: Rehabilitation Center, 1970 (Tube 73)
      Plot plan, sections, foundation plan, floor plan, elevations, finish schedule
    - Fellowship Hall, Inc.: Rehabilitation Center, 1970 (Tube 75)
      Portico, elevation, floor plans, details, sections
    - Fellowship Hall, Inc.: Rehabilitation Center, 1970 (Tube 74)
      Roof framing, plot plan, floor plan, heating and air, electrical plan
    - Fellowship Hall, Inc.: Rehabilitation Center (1 of 2), 1970 (Tube 107)
      Structural shop drawings
    - Fellowship Hall, Inc.: Rehabilitation Center (2 of 2), 1970 (Tube 108)
    - Fellowship Hall, Inc.: Rehabilitation Center, 1970-1971; 1970 1971 (Flatfolder 9)
    - Fellowship Hall, Inc.: Rehabilitation Center, 1971 (Tube 188)
    - Fellowship Hall, Inc.: Rehabilitation Center, 1971 (Flatfolder 2)
    - Fieldcrest Mills Technical Center, 1974 (Tube 117)
      Roof traffic pad
      Odell Associates Inc.; Eden (N.C.)
    - First Baptist Church: Electrical (Tube 90)
      Monroe (N.C.)
    - First Presbyterian Church, 1927 (Flatfolder 1)
      Heating plans, elevations, sections
      Harry Barton & Hobart Upjohn Architects; Greensboro (N.C.)
    - First Presbyterian Church, 1965-1966 (Tube 59)
    - First Presbyterian Church, 1966 (Tube 58)
      Entrance and retaining walls for parking lot
    - First Presbyterian Church: Apartment building, 1960 (Tube 87)
      Elevations, plans
    - First Presbyterian Church: Cemetery wall, 1964 (Tube 72)
    - Fish (Mr. and Mrs. Konrad) residence (Tube 49)
      Floor plans, elevations
    - Forest Lawn Cemetery: Woodroof lot (Tube 60)
    - Forest Lawn Cemetery: Woodroof lot #128 Sec. 2, 1971 (Tube 152)
    - Fourfifteen Corporation: Offices (Tube 68)
      Floor plans, elevations, specifications
    - Friendly Center, 1957 (Tube 131)
    - Front door residence, 1969 (Tube 177)
    - Gardner (Mr. Howard) store building (Tube 166)
    - Glascock Stove and Manufacturing Company, 1965 (Tube 68)
      Site plans, floor plans
    - Golden Touch Cleaners and Launderette, 1968 (Tube 189)
      Reidsville (N.C.)
    - Greensboro Country Club: Tennis pavilion, 1968 (Tube 89)
      Sections, plans
    - Greensboro Country Club: Tennis pavilion, 1968 (Tube 98)
      Plans, sections, elevations
    - Greensboro Country Club: Tennis pavilion, 1968 (Tube 90)
    - Greensboro Urban Area (1 of 2), 1967 (Tube 176)
    - Greensboro Urban Area (2 of 2), 1967 (Tube 177)
    - Guilford Mills Warehouse, 1967 (Tube 137)
      Reinforcing placing plan
    - King's Arms Apartments (Tube 72)
      Walking and paving plan
    - King's Arms Apartments, 1964 (Tube 55)
    - King's Arms Apartments for Johnston Properties, Inc., 1965 (Tube 146)
      Plot plan, sections, elevations, floor plans
    - Lambeth-Troxler Funeral Service, 1971 (Tube 49)
      Plot plan, heating plan, details, foundation plan, sections, floor plans, elevations
    - Leaksville Publishing Company: Additions, 1967 (Tube 78)
      Cover sheet
      Woodroof and MacRae, Architects, Inc.; Leaksville (N.C.)
    - Leaksville Publishing Company: Additions, 1967 (Tube 104)
      Sections, plans, elevations, details
      McMinn Norfleet & Wicker; Woodroof and MacRae, Architects, Inc.; Leaksville (N.C.)
    - Leaksville Publishing Company: Additions, 1967 (Tube 105)
    - Lutheran Church of Our Father, 1963 (Flatfolder 9)
      Loewenstein, Atkinson & Woodroof; Greensboro (N.C.)
    - Lutheran Church of Our Father, 1963 (Flatfolder 15)
    - M&M Mall Shopping Center, 1967-1971 (Tube 27)
      Site plan, elevations, plot plan
      Woodroof and Associates, Architects, Inc.; Madison (N.C.); Mayodan (N.C.)
    - M&M Mall Shopping Center, 1969-1971 (Tube 57)
      Finish schedule, elevations, reflected ceiling plan, floor plans, plot plan, section details
    - M&M Mall Shopping Center, 1969-1970 (Tube 49)
      Plot plan, elevations
    - M&M Mall Shopping Center, 1969-1970 (Tube 170)
      Rough grading plan
      Woodroof and MacRae, Architects, Inc.; Madison (N.C.); Mayodan (N.C.)
    - M&M Mall Shopping Center, 1969 (Tube 78)
      Woodroof and Associates, Architects, Inc.; Mayodan (N.C.); Madison (N.C.)
    - M&M Mall Shopping Center, 1969 (Tube 50)
      Grading plan, plot plan, sketches
    - M&M Mall Shopping Center, 1969 (Tube 113)
      Plot plan
    - M&M Mall Shopping Center, 1969 (Tube 55)
    - M&M Mall Shopping Center, 1970-1971 (Tube 38)
      Site plans, plot plans, floor plans, electrical plans, equipment schedule
    - M&M Mall Shopping Center, 1971 (Tube 25)
      Finish schedule, door schedule details, elevations, floor plans
    - M&M Mall Shopping Center, 1971 (Tube 26)
      Site plan, fixture plan, floor plans, equipment schedule, plumbing schedule
    - M&M Mall Shopping Center (1 of 2), 1971 (Flatfolder 15)
      Madison (N.C.); Mayodan (N.C.)
    - M&M Mall Shopping Center (2 of 2), 1971 (Flatfolder 16)
      Mayodan (N.C.); Madison (N.C.)
    - Marsh Furniture Company, 1963 (Flatfolder 15)
      Loewenstein-Atkinson Associates, Architects; High Point (N.C.)
    - McCall-Boykin Truck, Inc., 1965 (Tube 68)
      Preliminary plan
      Woodroof A. C. (Albert Cecil) Jr. 1920-1991; Baltimore (Md.)
    - McLendon, Brim, Brooks, Pierce & Daniels: Office suite, 1966 (Tube 169)
    - McLendon, Brim, Brooks, Pierce & Daniels: Office suite, 1966 (Tube 56)
    - McLendon, Brim, Holderness & Brooks, 1966 (Tube 59)
      Floor plan
      Woodroof and MacRae, Architects, Inc.
    - McMichael (Mr. and Mrs. Dalton): Proposed swimming pavilion (Tube 177)
      Woodroof A. C. (Albert Cecil) Jr. 1920-1991; Madison (N.C.)
    - McMichael (Mr. and Mrs. Dalton): Proposed swimming pavilion, 1967 (Tube 72)
      Woodroof and MacRae, Architects, Inc.; Madison (N.C.)
    - Moore & Turner residence, 1935 (Tube 139)
    - Morris (Lewis S.) proposed addition to residence, 1965 (Tube 68)
    - Norman (Mr. and Mrs. E.) residence: Royal Dornoch Golf Village, 1967 (Tube 76)
      Woodroof A. C. (Albert Cecil) Jr. 1920-1991; Pinehurst (N.C.)
    - Norman (Mr. and Mrs. E.) residence: Royal Dornoch Golf Village, 1967 (Tube 77)
    - Office building, 1964 (Tube 58)
    - Office building, 1964 (Tube 59)
    - Opportunity Center, 1966 (Tube 64)
      Electrical plan, floor plan, sketches
      Woodroof A. C. (Albert Cecil) Jr. 1920-1991; Wentworth (N.C.)
    - Opportunity Center, 1966 (Tube 168)
      Plumbing and heating plan
    - Orangeburg Mall, 1968 (Tube 184)
      Orangeburg (S.C.)
    - P. J. Coble Construction Company, 1968 (Flatfolder 9)
      Warehouse and shop addition
    - Patterson (Dr. and Mrs. Fred M.) residence: Proposed addition, 1953 (Tube 179)
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center (Tube 145)
      Illustrative site plan
      Woodroof, MacRae and Senell Architects; Reidsville (N.C.)
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center (Tube 58)
      Overall site plan
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center, 1967-1968 (Tube 7)
      Doors, plumbing plans, mechanical plans
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center, 1967-1968 (Tube 19)
      Elevations, shop plans, partial plans
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center, 1967-1968 (Tube 22)
      Floor plans, elevations, stie plan, details, door schedule
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center, 1967-1968 (Tube 54)
      Paving, planting
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center, 1967-1968 (Tube 21)
      Paving, planting, site work details, elevations, sections
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center, 1967-1968 (Tube 24)
      Topographical survey, grading, drainage, shop plans, mechanical plans
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center, 1967-1969 (Tube 43)
      Floor plans, sections
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center, 1967-1969 (Tube 45)
      Master plan, roof plan, elevations, floor plans, sections
      Woodroof and Associates, Architects, Inc.; Woodroof and MacRae, Architects, Inc.; Reidsville (N.C.)
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center, 1967-1970 (Tube 44)
      Sections, details, elevations
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center, 1967 (Tube 176)
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center, 1967 (Tube 18)
      Door and frame elevations, toilets, details, sign
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center, 1967 (Tube 3)
      Foundation plan, sections, panel elevations
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center, 1967 (Tube 168)
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center, 1967 (Tube 168)
      Overall site plan, planting, painting, signs
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center, 1967 (Tube 53)
      Planting, site work details, site plan, shop plans, elevations
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center, 1967 (Tube 10)
      Plumbing plans, site plan
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center, 1967 (Tube 62)
      Site plans
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center, 1967 (Tube 6)
      Site plan, paving plan, planting plan, shops
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center, 1967 (Tube 20)
      Sketches, plans
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center, 1967 (Tube 145)
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center, 1968-1969 (Tube 72)
      Floor plans, elevations, door schedule
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center, 1968-1970 (Tube 138)
      Master site plan
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center (1 of 5), 1968 (Tube 180)
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center (2 of 5), 1968 (Tube 184)
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center (3 of 5), 1968 (Tube 183)
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center (4 of 5), 1968 (Tube 182)
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center (5 of 5), 1968 (Tube 181)
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center (1 of 2), 1968 (Flatfolder 2)
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center (2 of 2), 1968 (Flatfolder 4)
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center, 1969 (Tube 170)
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center, 1969 (Tube 171)
      Plot plan, details
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Belk, 1969 (Flatfolder 10)
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Eckerd, Branch Bank, Roses, 1966-1968 (Tube 17)
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Phase B, 1969 (Tube 66)
      Lighting plan, fixture schedule, elevations, shop plans, details
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Phase B, 1969 (Tube 67)
      Proposed shops, site plan, floor plan, plot plan
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Phase B, East West Mall (1 of 2), 1970 (Tube 95)
      Schedule, detail, floor plans
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Phase B, East West Mall (2 of 2), 1970 (Tube 96)